John W. Tukey Papers 1937-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.117
American Philosophical Society
- Series IV. Princeton University, 1937-1987; 21 linear feet
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lecture Notes - Numbers and Statistical Theory, 1960; Folder 1
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lecture Notes - Numerical Analysis, 1960; Folder 2
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lecture notes for Graduate Courses, 1960; Folder 1
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lecture notes for Graduate Courses, 1960; Folder 2
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lecture Notes for Graduate Courses, 1960; Folder 3
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lecture Notes for Graduate Courses, 1960; Folder 3
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lecture notes on Analysis of Variance, 1954; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lecture Notes on Analysis of Variance, 1954; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures of Symbolic Logic (Prof. A. Church), 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Commutative Algebra (506), 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Commutative Algebra (Prof. S. Bochner), 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Complex Variables (517), 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Complex Variables (Prof. S. Bochner), 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Infinite Convolutions (Prof. A. Wintner), 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Infinite Convolutions (Prof. A. Wintner), 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Magnetism (Prof. J.H. VanVleck), 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Magnetisn (Prof. J. H. VanVleck), 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Organic Chemistry (53) Prof. E. S. Wallis, 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Organic Chemistry (Prof. E.S. Wallis), 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Symbolic Dynamics (Prof. M. Morse), 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Symbolic Dynamics (Prof. Marston Morse), 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Symbolic Logic (501) Prof. A. Church, 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Lectures on Topology (Prof. A.W. Tucker), 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Math 501 (Prof. Alonzo W. Church) Reference Notes, n.d.; 1 notebook
  - Tukey, John W. -- Memorandum on a Possible Graduate Program in Quantitative Methodology, 1963; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Memorandum on a Possible Graduate Program, 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- New Techniques, 1952 March 29; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Notes, Graduate Courses, 1958-1959; Folder 1
  - Tukey, John W. -- Notes, Graduate Courses, 1958; Folder 1
  - Tukey, John W. -- Notes, Graduate Courses, 1958-1959; Folder 2
  - Tukey, John W. -- Notes, Graduate Courses, 1958; Folder 2
  - Tukey, John W. -- Of Statistics, 1971 October 5; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Outline for an Introduction to Black Boxes and Cosines, 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Outline for An Introduction to Cosines and Their Estimation, 2 items
  - Tukey, John W. -- Possible Applications of Quartimax, 1966-1968; 5 items
  - Tukey, John W. -- Possible Applications of Quartimax -- and (Possibly) Stepwise -- Approaches in Frequency Analysis, 1966, 1968
  - Tukey, John W. -- Possible Courses in Statistics and Computing Science, 1966; 2 items
  - Tukey, John W. -- Possible Courses in Statistics and Computing Science, 1966; 5 items
  - Tukey, John W. -- Possible Program for Anita and Don, 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Project Overhead, 1961; 5 items
  - Tukey, John W. -- Questionaire Concerning the Annals, n.d.; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Reference Notes in Mathematics 501- Symbolic Logic. Prof. Alonzo W. Church, n.d.; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Research Proposal: Graphic Techniques, 1984-1985; 7 items
  - Tukey, John W. -- Some Comparative Results of Simple Location Estimates, 1973 March 7; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Some Questions and Answers About Regression -- As of May, 1975, 1975 May 1; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Statistician's Guide to Exploratory Data Analysis, Memo No. 5, 1977-1978; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Statistician's Guide to Exploratory Data Analysis, Memos, 1977-1978; 6 items
  - Tukey, John W. -- Statistician's Guide to Exploratory Data Analysis, Outline, 1977, May 10; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Statistician's Guide to Exploratory Data Analysis, 1977; 2 items
  - Tukey, John W. -- Statistics and Health Sciences at Princeton, 1966; 2 items
  - Tukey, John W. -- The Kendall Sum, 1950 February; 1 item
  - Tukey, John W. -- Un-meeting of the Un-committee on Un-small Data Sets, 1977 June 16; 1 item
  - Tukey, John -- Department Statement, 1 item
  - Undergraduate Instruction, 1966-1967; 2 items
  - United States Energy Research and Development, 1976 September 20; 1 item
  - United States. Army Research Office -- Mathematical Sciences Division, 1969; 3 items
  - United States. Office of Naval Research, 1978 July 6; 1 item
  - Various Means of Constructing Confidence Intervals, n.d.; 1 item
  - Venet, Theodore G., 1977 October 25; 1 item
  - Wagstaff, David A., 1979 September 20; 2 items
  - Wallis, W. Allen, 1978 December 19; 1 item
  - Watson, Geoffrey S., 1971-1977; 2 items
  - Weyl, F. Joachim, 1969 December 8; 1 item
  - Winer Workshop, 1964; 3 items
  - Wintner, Aurel, 1903- -- Asymptotic Distributions and Infinite Convolutions, 1937-1938; 1 item
  - Wold, Herman, 1977 April 20; 1 item
  - Wolfe, Tom, 1969 February 7; 1 item
  - Work on Statististical Method. -- Original - Notes for Class, n.d.; 1 item
  - Zehna, Peter W., 1978; 2 items
- Series V. Bell Laboratories, 1946-1985; 7.5 linear feet
  This series contains material from John W. Tukey’s career at Bell Laboratories, one spanning 40 years. Most of the material research and development projects at Bell Labs as well as memoranda concerning managerial issues. Among the material is a Management Attitude Survey Tukey participated in for a number of years beginning in 1940 and ending in 1957. There is substantial material concerning a lawsuit brought by the states of New Jersey and Indiana in which Tukey testified on rate determination. There is general correspondence as well as documentation of other projects and committees Tukey worked on while employed by Bell Labs, such as The President’s Science Advisory Committee and a number of folders with material about pollution. There are a number of appointment records and secretary’s records of correspondence books.
  - Addison-Wesley Publishing Company., 1977-1979; 18 items
  - Advisory Council on Research., 1961-1973; Folder 1
  - Advisory Council on Research., 1974-1980; Folder 2
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science., 1971-1973; 9 items
  - American Philosophical Society. Correspondence, 1973-1974; 35 items
  - American Statistical Association. Correspondence, 1956-1973; 18 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company Department of Operation and Engineering. Development of Existing Depreciation in Telephone Plant, 1955-1956; Folder 1
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company Department of Operation and Engineering. Development of Existing Depreciation in Telephone Plant, 1955-1956; Folder 2
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Attitude Surveys of Management People, 1954; Folder 1
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Factor Analysis - Non Management Survey, 1957; 7 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attittude Survey. Analysis, Plans, Reports, 1957-1958; 25 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. "System" Data., 1955; 12 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Background of the Bell System's Management Attitude Survey, 1958; 1 item
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Collected Material on Indices., 1957; Folder 1
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Collected Material on Indices, 1957; Folder 2
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Comments on the present situation of the management survey, 1957; 2 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Comployee N's, 1957; 14 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Computational error reports, 1958; 3 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Conference with Dr. Andrew Henry, 1955; 2 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Customer Attitude Trend Study., 1957; 3 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Data processing, 1958-1959; 4 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Education, 1955-1958; 17 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Factor Analysis - Non Management Survey, 1957; 9 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Factor Analysis - Siegman, 1955-1957; 5 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Intro, 1960; 2 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Memorandum for Mr. H. R. Maddox, 1955; 1 item
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Miscellaneous sub-studies, 1958; 12 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Notes. General Information, 1 item
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Notes., Folder 1
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Notes., Folder 2
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Notes., Folder 3
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Notes., 1959; Folder 4
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Notes., Folder 5
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Notes., Folder 6
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Notes., Folder 7
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Notes., Folder 8
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Procedure for Normalizing Items, 1958; 7 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Review of Attitude Survey Methodology, 1957; 1 item
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Revision. Recommendations., 1958-1959; 8 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Rural Urban, 1954-1958; 8 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Study Plan, 1957-1958; 10 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Study., 1957; 3 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Supplemental Coding, 1957; 3 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Surveys of supervisors, 1 item
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Suspense, 1958; 25 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Test Data Cards., 64 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Trends of Field Work Performance., 1958; 8 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Variance of responses, 1957-1958; 4 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Management Attitude Survey. Years, Distributions - Service, 1957-1958; 9 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Manual for Conducting Attitude Surveys of Management People, 1954; Folder 1
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Manual for Conducting Attitude Surveys of Management People, 1954; Folder 2
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Manual for Conducting Attitude Surveys of Management People, 1954; Folder 3
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Tukey Testimony Transcript, 1949-1952; 3 items
  - American Telephone and Telegraph. Company. Management Attitude Survey. Charts for Kappel., 1960; 3 items
  - ANAC. Meeting, 1973; 3 items
  - Anscombe, Francis J., 1972, January 3; 1 item
  - AT and T Bell Laboratories Information Sciences Division. Penehighest (Penetop) System Considerations, 1985; 4 items
  - AT and T Systems Council. Systems Architecture Workshop, 1984; 4 items
  - Attrition of Engineers, 1962; 3 items
  - Barnes, D. H. The Relation and Effect of Scanning Rate to the Application of Usage Data for Traffic Engineering of Short, Constant Holding Time Circuits, 1953; 2 items
  - Barnett, George A. and Joseph Woelfel. On the Dimensionality of Psychological Processes, 1976; 2 items
  - Bell Laboratories Library Committee. Draft Report of the Special Meeting of the Library Committee, 1977; 1 item
  - Bell Laboratories, Public Relations and Publication Division. Management Topics, 1965-1967; 15 items
  - Bell Laboratories. 1976 Report of the Task Group on Technical Memoranda, 1977; 1 item
  - Bell Laboratories. Area 10 - General, 1976-1980; 3 items
  - Bell Laboratories. Area 10 Affirmative Action Committee, 1971-1972; Folder 1
  - Bell Laboratories. Area 10 Affirmative Action Committee, 1973-1979; Folder 2
  - Bell Laboratories. Employee Communications Study, 1983; 3 items
  - Bell Laboratories. Initial Response to Comments Related to X-ray Fit Paper by J. M. Landwehr, 1970; 2 items
  - Bell Laboratories. Progress Reports for Center 1127, 1982-1983; 77 items
  - Bell Laboratories. Project S.E.E.D., 1971; 2 items
  - Bell Laboratories. Skytop Conferences, 1976-1980; 13 items
  - Bell Laboratories. Task Force on On-Line Literature Searching, 1976; 5 items
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania - Condition of Plant 1954. Sampling Procedures for Selecting Items to be Inspected, 2 items
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania Legal Department., 1949; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The., 1956; 9 items
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Charts Illustrative of Sampling Principles, Company Exhibit 16A, n.d.; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Comparison of Continuing Property Records, 1954; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Condition of Plant - 1948, 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Condition of Plant - 1948, Folder 1
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Condition of Plant - 1948, Folder 2
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Condition of Plant - 1948, Folder 3
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Condition of Plant - 1954, 1956; 6 items
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Conflict of Interest Questionnaire, 1960; 2 items
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Direct Testimony of J. W. Tukey, n.d.; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. General, 1948
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission v The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, 1956; Folder 01
    Direct Testimony of Murdock McLeod. RE: Physical Condition of Telephone Plant Other Than Land and Buildings
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission v The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, n.d.; Folder 02
    Complaint Docket No. 16556. Company Exhibit No. 11.
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission v The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, 1948; Folder 03
    Complaint Docket No 14499. Company Exhibits 16A, 16B, 16C
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission v The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, n.d.; Folder 04
    Complaint Docket NO. 14499. Direct Testimony of Dr. J. W. Tukey RE Sampling Methods and Procedures in RE Depreciation
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission v The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, 1949-1956; Folder 05
    Direct Testimony of Dr. John W. Tukey. Sampling Methods and Procedures
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission v The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, n.d.; Folder 06
    Testimony of John W. Tukey on the Theory of Sampling and the Application of Sampling to Conditioning Telephone Plant
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission v The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, 1948; Folder 07
    Sampling Testimony (Tukey)
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission v The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, Folder 08
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission v The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, 1948; Folder 09
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission v The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, 1950; Folder 10
    Testimony of Dr. W. Edwards Deming on the Sampling Procedures for the Physical Condition of Plant
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission v The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, n.d.; Folder 11
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission v The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, n.d.; Folder 12
    Outlines of qualifications to present testimony before New Jersey Board of Public Utility Commissioners
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Sampling Instructions (Directions for Selecting the Individuals Items of Plant to be Conditioned) Company Exhibit no 16B, 1948 February 6; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Sampling Materials, 1948-1949; Folder 1
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Sampling Materials, 1948-1949; Folder 2
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, The. Testimony, 1949-1952; 9 items
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories II. Research Notebook. William G. French., 1969-1970; 1 ntoebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories Incorporated. Secretary's Record of Correspondence, 1961 July-1962 December 19; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories Incorporated. Secretary's Record of Correspondence, 1958 August 1 - 1963 October 11; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories Incorporated. Secretary's Record of Correspondence, 1960 February - 1961 July; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories Incorporated. Secretary's Record of Correspondence, 1956 June 25-1958 July 31; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories Incorporated. Secretary's Record of Correspondence, 1963 October 18; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories Incorporated. Secretary's Record of Correspondence, 1964 June 3; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories Incorporated. Secretary's Record of Correspondence, 1962 December 20-1964 June 2; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories Incorporated. Secretary's Record of Correspondence, 1965 November 22-1967 June 30; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories Incorporated. Secretary's Record of Correspondence, 1958 August 4 - 1960 February 18; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories Incorporated. Secretary's Record of Correspondence, 1967 July 5 - 1972 October 12; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Bell Telephone Exhibit New York World's Fair 1959, 3 items
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Organization, 1963; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research and Lecture Notebook, 1952; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research and Patent Pictorial Directory, 1954-1963; 2 items
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research Notebook. G. William Tasker., 1973-1974; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research notebook. G. William Tasker., 1975; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research notebook. J. Shreiver, 1980; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research Notebook. J. W. Shieber., 1976-1977; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research notebook. J.M. Shiever, 1979; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research Notebook. Paul Bergh., 1978; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research notebook. William French., 1969; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research notebook. William G. French., 1978-1979; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research notebook. William G. French., 1973-1975; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research Notebook. William G. French, 1979-1979; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research Notebook. William G. French, 1977-1978; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research Notebook. William G. French, 1976-1977; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research notebook. William G. French, 1979; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research Notebooks. G. William Tasker., 1973; 1 ntoebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research Notebooks. J. M. Shiever, 1977-1978; 1 notebook
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories. Research Notebooks., 1973; 1 notebook
  - Bell, R. J. Some Pioneers ofo Fourier Transform Spectroscopy, n.d.; 1 item
  - Bethe, A, W. K.H. Panofsky and J. W. Tukey. Notes on Jobs of Importance in Connection with the Dectection and Identification of Seismic Events, 1 item
  - Bochner, Arthur P. and Mary Anne Fitzpatrick. Multivariate Analysis of Variance: Techniques, Models, and Applications in Communication Research, 1977; 1 item
  - Bohannan, Paul and Richard Rawlins. Prologomena to a Study of Aggression, 2 items
  - Bose, R. C. and Shanti S. Gupta. Moments of Order Statistics From a Normal Population, 1959; 2 items
  - Bourne, S. R. and S. C. Johnson. Recent Visits to Xerox PARC, 1 item
  - Bowles, Samuel and Henry M. Levin. Equality of Educational Opportunity, 1967; 1 item
  - Brillinger, David R., 1960; 3 items
  - Brown, David M. Comployee Tables Program, 1959; 1 item
  - Brown, W. S. Alpak Applications and DID Cards, 1965 January 18; 2 items
  - Buchsbaum, S. J., 1974; 6 items
  - Calhoun, John B. the Influence of "Social Velocity" on the Sequence and Duration of Behaviors of Rats, 1962; 1 item
  - California Institute of Technology Division of the Geological Sciences., 1960; 1 item
  - Cappella, Joseph N. Structural Equation Modeling: An Introduction, 1977; 1 item
  - Churchman, C. West. F.C.C. Testimony, 1967; 1 item
  - Ciminera, Joseph L, Joseph F. Heyse, Nathan Mantel, and John W. Tukey. Tumorigenicity Assays, Including Use of the Jackknife, 1979; 7 items
  - Citizens' Commission on Science, Law and the Food Supply. Work and Plans of the Citizens' Commission, 1973-1975; 16 items
  - Cleveland, William S. and Robert McGill. The Many Faces of a Scatterplot, 1984; 1 item
  - Coale, Ansley J. Analysis of the Education of Scientists, 1962; 1 item
  - Committee for Economic Development., 1971; 8 items
  - Committee for Economic Development. More Effective Programs for a Cleaner Environment, 1973; 8 items
  - Committee on Computers in Education., 1973; 8 items
  - Committee On Scholarly Communication with the People's Republic of China. China in the Schools: Directions and Priorities, 1973; 3 items
  - Committee on Statistics. Exploratory Conference on Uses of Computers in Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry and Statistics, 1967; 1 item
  - Computer Science and Statistics. Sixth Annual Symposium on the Interface, 1972; 3 items
  - Computer Usage Company, Inc. Management Attitude Survey, 1958 December 2; 2 items
  - Computing and Computer Graphics, 1965; 5 items
  - Conference on Sampling Procedures, 1952-1953; 13 items
  - Danes, Jeffrey E. and Joseph Woelfel. Models for the Metric Multidimensional Analysis of Communication, Conception and Change, 2 items
  - Danes, Jeffrey E. and Joseph Woelfel. New Techniques for the Multidimensional Analysis of Communication, Conception, and Change, 1977; 2 items
  - Data Analysis, 1975-1981; 4 items
  - Davis, Dennis K. Time Series Analysis and Spectral Analysis, 1977; 2 items
  - de Kleer, Johan and Brian C. Williams. Diagnosing Multiple Faults, 1985; 2 items